lifecapsulenutrition.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Life Capsule Nutrition

**Legal Notice**

LIFE CAPSULE is edited by 50 Square OÜ 50 Square OÜ, SARL with capital of 2,500 euros Headquarters: Narva mnt 5, Tallinn 10117, Estonia Publication Director: Pierre Coutilard EU VAT: EE101769664 Phone: 09 77 55 59 90

**Statement of Privacy / Data Protection - Data Protection Act** **Introduction**

The information collected on this site is subject to data processing intended for the exclusive use of LIFE CAPSULE.

LIFE CAPSULE is committed to protecting the privacy of its customers and visitors to its websites, and views the protection of personal data as being of fundamental importance for the operation of its business. The personal data of customers and site visitors are protected and treated with the utmost care. LIFE CAPSULE is in compliance with the requirements of the Data Protection Act of 6 January 1978.

Under the Data Protection Act of 6 January 1978, you have a right to access, modification, cancellation and opposition to the data. If you wish to exercise these rights, please contact our customer service at 09 77 55 59 90 or write to support@GetLifeCapsule.com

We undertake not to disclose to third parties information about you unless you give us permission.

**Your consent**

By using our site you accept our privacy policy.

**Processing of personal data**

The data collected by the LIFE CAPSULE is to provide the services requested. Your personal details are stored when you purchase a subscription to a newsletter or order a book

or product, have subscribed to one of our services, or have opened an Internet account. The stored personal data is data such as contact details, information about payments, invoices, ordered products, business data (company and position held) and / or the interest you have shown in a product or service.

LIFE CAPSULE uses this information to deliver the services you have subscribed to the administrative and business processing services (delivery, opening access rights, billing, etc.), and inform you of new products and services offered by LIFE CAPSULE.

**How do we protect your information?**

We are implementing a series of security measures to ensure the security of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

These security measures include: password protected directories to protect your information, an SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and the data is sent over a secure web or PCI scanning to proactively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities.

We offer the use of a secure server. Sensitive information / credit card information provided is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, to then be encrypted in the database of our payment gateway provider, accessible only by authorized persons, with specific access rights to such systems, and required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financial data, etc.) will not be stored in our servers.

**Your email address**

If you provided your email address (e.g. to subscribe to a newsletter), it can be used to inform you of other products and services offered by LIFE CAPSULE that may interest you. If you do not wish to receive this information, you can exercise your right of access, modification, cancellation and opposition to your data at any time by contacting our Customer Service by email support @ lifecapsulenutrition.com .

**Navigation and IP History**

To improve the quality of its sites, and Internet services, LIFE CAPSULE collects data concerning navigation on its websites. These data are not personal.

LIFE CAPSULE also uses the IP address of your computer for this purpose. The IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Internet.

This information can be used to study the use of the site for analysis and reporting, to display information geographically targeted (geo-targeting), or to adapt the information or services based navigation.

In general, IP addresses are not linked to any information that could identify you, unless you have given your express permission for this.

**Use of Cookies by LIFE CAPSULE**

A cookie is a result of information sent by a website to a computer in the form of a small data file. Cookies are useful for easy customization of your access to our online services. They can be used for authentication, session and store specific information such as preferences on a website or the content of an electronic shopping cart. Storage of cookies is done through the web browser used by the user (e.g. Internet Explorer).

There are two types of cookies:

  *  Session cookies are deleted e d from your computer when you close your browser. 
  *  Permanent cookies are stock e d on your computer after è s closing the browser. Cookies are however anonymous and are in no way used to collect personal information. LIFE CAPSULE uses cookies to allow and facilitate electronic communication, provide online services subscribed by subscribers, analyze site usage with the aim of improving the quality of its sites, collect general data (not nominative) on its customers for the purposes of targeted communication, including the provision of targeted information on products or services provided by LIFE CAPSULE. Website LIFE CAPSULE broadcast advertising also use "cookies" for advertising purposes, to direct certain advertisements based on the geographic area of Internet and or advertising that will present a number of times limited by the recipient. **Refusal of cookies** You are free to accept or decline cookies by configuring your browser (disabling or all of the cookies - see your web browser manual or help function). Disabling cookies may result in the unavailability of certain services which they are associated. It does not prevent access to non-reserved areas of the site. Furthermore, we keep track of connections to our sites, including their origin. This information is used for purposes of statistical analysis. The corresponding data do not contain personal data and are destroyed after use. **Hyperlinks**

Users are formally informed that the sites they can access through hyperlinks do not all belong to LIFE CAPSULE. LIFE CAPSULE is not responsible for the content of information provided on sites that do not belong to him, under the activation of the hyperlink.

**Do we disclose information to third parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, operate our business or service to you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also disclose your information when we believe it is necessary to comply with the law, to implement policies of our site and to protect our rights, our property, our security or those / that of others. However, non-identifiable information may be provided to third parties for commercial or advertising purposes or other.

**Legal notice to users**

The user agrees to the characteristics and limitations of the Internet and, in particular, recognize:

  *   Have knowledge of the nature of the I nternet and in particular its technical performance and response t ime to consult, question or transfer t he data or information. 
  *  The communication by the u ser to third parties of his credentials and a gernal way of any information found by the user as personal or confidential is at risk 
  *  That it is up to the user to take all appropriate measures to protect its own data and or software from contamination by virus on the Internet 
  *  That data circulating on the Internet can be regulated in terms of use or protect by right of prosperity. Generally, the user is solely responsible for the selection, use and interpretation of the data he consults, questions and transfers on the Internet and use online services offered by LIFE CAPSULE. **Subject to change** LIFE CAPSULE reserves the right to make changes to this privacy statement. Visitors and clients' websites LIFE CAPSULE are encouraged to regularly visit this privacy statement to consult the latest version of the group's privacy policy. For any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us using the contact information below.
